Id,text,named_ents
0,"Murray McLauchlan is one of Canada's most highly regarded singer/songwriters and with good cause. Over a 48-year career, he has released 19 albums and....","[{'Murray McLauchlan': 'PERSON'}, {'one': 'CARDINAL'}, {'Canada': 'GPE'}, {'48-year': 'CARDINAL'}, {'19': 'CARDINAL'}]"
1,"For the fourth week of FebFest there will be lots of outdoor activities with an ice stock demo, skating and more! This week's Toast to Tapas theme will be an all time Canadian favourite, bacon. As an added bonus,....","[{'the fourth week of FebFest': 'DATE'}, {'week': 'DATE'}, {'Toast': 'ORG'}, {'Canadian': 'NORP'}]"
2,Bundle up the little kids and take them to Boucher Park on Clarence Street just around the corner from Springer Market Square and let the kids enjoy the ice slides and ice sculptures. Boucher Park will be open for the whole month of February (weather permitting) in the heart of downtown Kingston ...,"[{'Bundle': 'GPE'}, {'Boucher Park': 'LOC'}, {'Clarence Street': 'FAC'}, {'Springer Market Square': 'FAC'}, {'Boucher Park': 'FAC'}, {'the whole month of February': 'DATE'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
3,"Spring Market Square - come and enjoy a lovely, outdoor, skate to music in the historical downtown of Kingston. This public skate is free to the public and makes for a great family outing. Hours of operation are from 8 am to 10 pm Monday to Sunday ....","[{'Kingston': 'GPE'}, {'8 am to 10 pm': 'TIME'}, {'Monday': 'DATE'}, {'Sunday': 'DATE'}]"
4,"If you’ve ever gone out for a pint in the city, chances are you’ve met Greg Ball. He’s a Kingston bartender who just happens to be signed with Ching Music. The....","[{'Greg Ball': 'PERSON'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}, {'Ching Music': 'ORG'}]"
5,Experiential Tourism is growing in popularity come take part in a cool ( not literally) artisan experience. Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery offers ....,[{'Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery': 'ORG'}]
6,You better come grab your seat early! This local favourite will pack our lounge! You never know who will join Chris Jackson on stage...,[{'Chris Jackson': 'PERSON'}]
7,Skate indoors on the large NHL - sized ice pad at The Centre 70 Arena. This leisurely skate is open to all ages and is monitored by the Skate Patrol...,"[{'NHL': 'ORG'}, {'The Centre 70 Arena': 'FAC'}, {'the Skate Patrol': 'WORK_OF_ART'}]"
8,"The Ice Cold Comedy Festival returns for its third year with some brand new venues, fresh new faces and some of our past favourites.",[{'its third year': 'DATE'}]
9,"Hosted by local legend and musical veteran, Scotty, Open Mic kicks off at 7pm, and ends when our taps- and your vocals- run dry! No sign-up necessary and a......","[{'Scotty': 'PERSON'}, {'Open Mic': 'PERSON'}, {'7pm': 'TIME'}]"
10,"Join us for Melos' annual fundraiser: From Cloisters to Carnival! Enjoy Melos' best selections of Early Music under St George's heavenly dome, along with wine, food, and.....","[{'Melos': 'ORG'}, {'annual': 'DATE'}, {""Enjoy Melos'"": 'PERSON'}, {'Early Music': 'ORG'}, {'George': 'PERSON'}]"
11,"Greg Runions and his all-star Canadian septet present a concert of original and classic jazz music. The ensemble will perform repertoire from the groups 1996 and 2017 recordings plus standards from Duke Ellington's musical partner, the great jazz .....","[{'Greg Runions': 'PERSON'}, {'Canadian': 'NORP'}, {'1996': 'DATE'}, {'2017': 'DATE'}, {""Duke Ellington's"": 'PERSON'}]"
12,Bundle up the little kids and take them to Boucher Park on Clarence Street just around the corner from Springer Market Square and let the kids enjoy the ice slides and ice sculptures. Boucher Park will be open for the whole month of February (weather permitting) in the heart of downtown Kingston ...,"[{'Bundle': 'GPE'}, {'Boucher Park': 'LOC'}, {'Clarence Street': 'FAC'}, {'Springer Market Square': 'FAC'}, {'Boucher Park': 'FAC'}, {'the whole month of February': 'DATE'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
13,"Spring Market Square - come and enjoy a lovely, outdoor, skate to music in the historical downtown of Kingston. This public skate is free to the public and makes for a great family outing. Hours of operation are from 8 am to 10 pm Monday to Sunday ....","[{'Kingston': 'GPE'}, {'8 am to 10 pm': 'TIME'}, {'Monday': 'DATE'}, {'Sunday': 'DATE'}]"
14,"IT'S HERE!! The 2020 Tim Hortons Brier, presented by AGI, will be played Feb. 29-March 8 at Leon’s Centre in downtown Kingston.The Tim Hortons Brier is probably the truest of any Canadian sporting championship.....","[{'2020': 'DATE'}, {'Tim Hortons Brier': 'PERSON'}, {'AGI': 'ORG'}, {'Feb. 29-March 8': 'DATE'}, {'Leon’s Centre': 'FAC'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}, {'The Tim Hortons Brier': 'PERSON'}, {'Canadian': 'NORP'}]"
15,"If you’ve ever gone out for a pint in the city, chances are you’ve met Greg Ball. He’s a Kingston bartender who just happens to be signed with....","[{'Greg Ball': 'PERSON'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
16,"Lace up your sneakers! Starting April 1st, come join members of the Riverhead team for a bi-weekly 3k walk/run. We will increase distances overtime to keep pace with.....",[{'April 1st': 'DATE'}]
17,Enjoy a family skate on the NHL sized ice pads and then warm up afterwards in the dressing rooms that have in-floor heating. Participants of all ages can enjoy a leisurely skate around the ice surface ...,[{'NHL': 'ORG'}]
18,Come and enjoy Monday night Jazz downtown at Musiikki Cafe.  The number 1 venue for music of all kinds and all places.  Come in and enjoy an expertly made ...,"[{'Monday': 'DATE'}, {'night': 'TIME'}, {'Musiikki Cafe': 'FAC'}, {'1': 'CARDINAL'}]"
19,Drop on over to the Brier Patch Fan Zone immediately following the end of tonight’s draw for a Music Video Dance Party....,"[{'Brier Patch Fan Zone': 'GPE'}, {'tonight': 'TIME'}, {'a Music Video Dance Party': 'ORG'}]"
20,Bundle up the little kids and take them to Boucher Park on Clarence Street just around the corner from Springer Market Square and let the kids enjoy the ice slides and ice sculptures. Boucher Park will be open for the whole month of February (weather permitting) in the heart of downtown Kingston ...,"[{'Bundle': 'GPE'}, {'Boucher Park': 'LOC'}, {'Clarence Street': 'FAC'}, {'Springer Market Square': 'FAC'}, {'Boucher Park': 'FAC'}, {'the whole month of February': 'DATE'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
21,Enjoy a lovely ice skate with the whole family at Kingston Memorial Centre where the skate patrol are on the ice to monitor the program and are there to provide assistance when required.,[{'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}]
22,"The Art Noise Gallery is back this March to welcome Artist Bob Young. Bob completed a BFA (Visual Art — Studio) at York University, Toronto, and an","[{'The Art Noise Gallery': 'ORG'}, {'this March': 'DATE'}, {'Artist Bob Young': 'PERSON'}, {'Bob': 'PERSON'}, {'BFA (Visual Art — Studio': 'ORG'}, {'York University': 'ORG'}, {'Toronto': 'GPE'}]"
23,"Your family will enjoy the familiar music and story of Anna, Elsa, Kristoff, Hans, Olaf and Sven along with a cast of colourful characters in this student-acted.....","[{'Anna, Elsa, Kristoff, Hans, Olaf': 'ORG'}, {'Sven': 'DATE'}]"
24,"ONE NIGHT ONLY! ""Legends Show"" brings you some of the world's most exciting performers live on stage. Accompanied by the ""Rockin' Royals Band"", this show will feature incredible Tributes to Music Hits from the 50s and 60s....","[{'ONE': 'CARDINAL'}, {'Legends Show': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, {'Tributes': 'ORG'}, {'Music Hits': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, {'50s and 60s': 'DATE'}]"
25,"Jordan Edward Benjamin, know professionally as grandson, is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter and musician currently signed to Fueled by Ramen and RCA Records. ...","[{'Jordan Edward Benjamin': 'PERSON'}, {'Canadian-American': 'NORP'}, {'Fueled': 'ORG'}, {'Ramen': 'NORP'}, {'RCA Records': 'ORG'}]"
26,"Haunting locals and newcomers alike, this tour takes you through Kingston’s old Sydenham Ward. It features haunted hotels, hidden burial grounds, grave robbing, hangings at the old courthouse, and Kingston’s famous....","[{'Kingston': 'GPE'}, {'Sydenham Ward': 'FAC'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
27,Over 500 songs in the repertoire of The Goodnight Irenes. They perform in an intimate venue where the specialty coffee is fine and the whiskey is smooth ...,[{'500': 'CARDINAL'}]
28,"If you’ve ever gone out for a pint in the city, chances are you’ve met Greg Ball. He’s a Kingston bartender who just happens to be signed with....","[{'Greg Ball': 'PERSON'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
29,"Enjoy a leisurely skate with friends and family at Centre 70 Arena, 100 Days Road during  the winter season from 4 pm to 5 pm.  The Skate Patrol are on the....","[{'Centre 70 Arena': 'ORG'}, {'100 Days Road': 'CARDINAL'}, {'the winter season': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm to 5 pm': 'TIME'}, {'The Skate Patrol': 'PERSON'}]"
30,"The Art Noise Gallery is back this March to welcome Artist Bob Young. Bob completed a BFA (Visual Art — Studio) at York University, Toronto, and an","[{'The Art Noise Gallery': 'ORG'}, {'this March': 'DATE'}, {'Artist Bob Young': 'PERSON'}, {'Bob': 'PERSON'}, {'BFA (Visual Art — Studio': 'ORG'}, {'York University': 'ORG'}, {'Toronto': 'GPE'}]"
31,Experiential Tourism is growing in popularity come take part in a cool ( not literally) artisan experience. Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery offers ....,[{'Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery': 'ORG'}]
32,You better come grab your seat early! This local favourite will pack our lounge! You never know who will join Chris Jackson on stage...,[{'Chris Jackson': 'PERSON'}]
33,"The band has a wide genre including alternative rock, power pop, punk rock, Emo and pop punk.  The band has enjoyed a course marked by steady output, frequent touring and ...",[]
34,"Hosted by local legend and musical veteran, Scotty, Open Mic kicks off at 7pm, and ends when our taps- and your vocals- run dry! No sign-up necessary and a......","[{'Scotty': 'PERSON'}, {'Open Mic': 'PERSON'}, {'7pm': 'TIME'}]"
35,"Hey Guys,I want to apologize to anyone who has been inconvenienced or disappointed by the date changes on my upcoming tour. I promise these changes are for a very good reason and we have some exciting announcements coming soon! In the meantime,....",[]
36,"Sherlock Holmes is dead. At so it is assumed. The world knows the great detective went over the falls at Reichenbach with his nemesis Professor Moriarty. But as Holmes' body was never retrieved, a number of frauds, fakes, and charlatans have come.......","[{'Reichenbach': 'PERSON'}, {'Moriarty': 'PERSON'}, {'Holmes': 'PERSON'}]"
37,"Our season-long celebration comes to a magnificent close. We complete our Beethoven cycle in a grand finale featuring his nimble and lithe eighth symphony alongside his mighty ninth, the Ode to Joy. Happy 250th Ludwig!...","[{'Beethoven': 'PERSON'}, {'eighth': 'ORDINAL'}, {'ninth': 'ORDINAL'}, {'Joy': 'PERSON'}, {'250th Ludwig': 'PERSON'}]"
38,"If you’ve ever gone out for a pint in the city, chances are you’ve met Greg Ball. He’s a Kingston bartender who just happens to be signed with....","[{'Greg Ball': 'PERSON'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
39,Enjoy a leisurely skate with the family on the NHL-sized ice pads and warm-up afterwards in the dressing rooms with radiant in-door heating ...,[{'NHL': 'ORG'}]
40,Bring everyone in the family out to our annual frog hike. You’ll learn about the different frogs that live at Little Cataraqui Creek and go on a short walk to listen for frog....,"[{'annual': 'DATE'}, {'Little Cataraqui Creek': 'FAC'}]"
41,"The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market is open year-around and sells an assortment of fresh foods, baked goods, crafts and prepared food from....","[{""The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market"": 'ORG'}]"
42,Enjoy indoor ice skating with the whole family at Kingston Memorial Centre each Sunday during the winter season from 12 pm to 2 pm.  Kingston Memorial Centre is situated...,"[{'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}, {'Sunday': 'DATE'}, {'the winter season': 'DATE'}, {'12 pm to': 'QUANTITY'}, {'2 pm': 'TIME'}, {' ': 'ORDINAL'}, {'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}]"
43,"Swordwall started 8 years ago when some friends working at a restaurant together decided to name the magnetic knife holder in their kitchen, the ""sword wall"".These ...",[{'8 years ago': 'DATE'}]
44,Enjoy a family skate on the NHL sized ice pads and then warm up afterwards in the dressing rooms that have in-floor heating. Participants of all ages can enjoy a leisurely skate around the ice surface ...,[{'NHL': 'ORG'}]
45,Come and enjoy Monday night Jazz downtown at Musiikki Cafe.  The number 1 venue for music of all kinds and all places.  Come in and enjoy an expertly made ...,"[{'Monday': 'DATE'}, {'night': 'TIME'}, {'Musiikki Cafe': 'FAC'}, {'1': 'CARDINAL'}]"
46,"It’s a 30-person bike you ride with your coworkers. But it’s also a ridiculously fun team-building event: hang out with work friends, enjoy some fresh air and raise money for a great....",[{'30-person': 'CARDINAL'}]
47, Join Forest Therapy Guide Stana Luxford Oddie on a winter Forest Therapy walk.  A forest therapy walk is a healing and connective practice that provides the opportunity to deepen your......,"[{'winter': 'DATE'}, {'Forest Therapy': 'ORG'}]"
48,"Experience the scents & sounds of New Orleans  with Jazz, Cajun, Zydeco and R&B with Spencer Evans as you sail through the beautiful Thousand Islands aboard The Island Star...","[{'New Orleans': 'GPE'}, {'Jazz': 'ORG'}, {'Cajun': 'ORG'}, {'Zydeco': 'ORG'}, {'R&B': 'ORG'}, {'Spencer Evans': 'PERSON'}, {'Thousand Islands': 'FAC'}, {'The Island Star': 'FAC'}]"
49,"If you’ve ever gone out for a pint in the city, chances are you’ve met Greg Ball. He’s a Kingston bartender who just happens to be signed with....","[{'Greg Ball': 'PERSON'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
50,"Enjoy a leisurely skate with friends and family at Centre 70 Arena, 100 Days Road during  the winter season from 4 pm to 5 pm.  The Skate Patrol are on the....","[{'Centre 70 Arena': 'ORG'}, {'100 Days Road': 'CARDINAL'}, {'the winter season': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm to 5 pm': 'TIME'}, {'The Skate Patrol': 'PERSON'}]"
51,"We shuck ’em, you slurp ’em! Tuesday, starting at 4 pm enjoy fresh oysters on the half shell in the Taproom. Shucked to order, paired with Capers homemade.....","[{'Tuesday': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm': 'TIME'}, {'half': 'CARDINAL'}, {'Taproom': 'GPE'}]"
52,"Enjoy a leisurely skate with friends and family at Centre 70 Arena, 100 Days Road during  the winter season from 4 pm to 5 pm.  The Skate Patrol are on the....","[{'Centre 70 Arena': 'ORG'}, {'100 Days Road': 'CARDINAL'}, {'the winter season': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm to 5 pm': 'TIME'}, {'The Skate Patrol': 'PERSON'}]"
53,"We shuck ’em, you slurp ’em! Tuesday, starting at 4 pm enjoy fresh oysters on the half shell in the Taproom. Shucked to order, paired with Capers homemade.....","[{'Tuesday': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm': 'TIME'}, {'half': 'CARDINAL'}, {'Taproom': 'GPE'}]"
54,"A tradition among jazz lovers, Tuesday Night Jazz at Olivea ...",[{'Tuesday': 'DATE'}]
55,Expand your skill with acrylic paints. This class is made up of working on a series of panels using a variety of painting styles and applications to develop surface textures.....,[]
56,"An Irish Seisiún is an informal gathering at which people play traditional Irish music. All are welcome to bring their instrument and join in on the fun, every Tuesday at The Toucan!...","[{'An Irish Seisiún': 'GPE'}, {'Irish': 'NORP'}, {'Toucan': 'NORP'}]"
57,Enjoy a lovely ice skate with the whole family at Kingston Memorial Centre where the skate patrol are on the ice to monitor the program and are there to provide assistance when required.,[{'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}]
58,"If you’ve ever gone out for a pint in the city, chances are you’ve met Greg Ball. He’s a Kingston bartender who just happens to be signed with....","[{'Greg Ball': 'PERSON'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
59,"It’s bingo with a twist! Get ready to sing and dance with your host Amanda McCauley. Prizes to be won, and the winner of each round wins a 4-pack of delicious Riverhead.....","[{'Amanda McCauley': 'PERSON'}, {'Prizes': 'PERSON'}, {'4-pack': 'CARDINAL'}]"
60,Experiential Tourism is growing in popularity come take part in a cool ( not literally) artisan experience. Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery offers ....,[{'Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery': 'ORG'}]
61,You better come grab your seat early! This local favourite will pack our lounge! You never know who will join Chris Jackson on stage...,[{'Chris Jackson': 'PERSON'}]
62,"Hosted by local legend and musical veteran, Scotty, Open Mic kicks off at 7pm, and ends when our taps- and your vocals- run dry! No sign-up necessary and a......","[{'Scotty': 'PERSON'}, {'Open Mic': 'PERSON'}, {'7pm': 'TIME'}]"
63,Enjoy a leisurely skate with the family on the NHL-sized ice pads and warm-up afterwards in the dressing rooms with radiant in-door heating ...,[{'NHL': 'ORG'}]
64,"It’s bingo with a twist! Get ready to sing and dance with your host Amanda McCauley. Prizes to be won, and the winner of each round wins a 4-pack of delicious Riverhead.....","[{'Amanda McCauley': 'PERSON'}, {'Prizes': 'PERSON'}, {'4-pack': 'CARDINAL'}]"
65,Experiential Tourism is growing in popularity come take part in a cool ( not literally) artisan experience. Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery offers ....,[{'Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery': 'ORG'}]
66,You better come grab your seat early! This local favourite will pack our lounge! You never know who will join Chris Jackson on stage...,[{'Chris Jackson': 'PERSON'}]
67,"Hosted by local legend and musical veteran, Scotty, Open Mic kicks off at 7pm, and ends when our taps- and your vocals- run dry! No sign-up necessary and a......","[{'Scotty': 'PERSON'}, {'Open Mic': 'PERSON'}, {'7pm': 'TIME'}]"
68,Enjoy a leisurely skate with the family on the NHL-sized ice pads and warm-up afterwards in the dressing rooms with radiant in-door heating ...,[{'NHL': 'ORG'}]
69,"The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market is open year-around and sells an assortment of fresh foods, baked goods, crafts and prepared food from....","[{""The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market"": 'ORG'}]"
70,Enjoy indoor ice skating with the whole family at Kingston Memorial Centre each Sunday during the winter season from 12 pm to 2 pm.  Kingston Memorial Centre is situated...,"[{'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}, {'Sunday': 'DATE'}, {'the winter season': 'DATE'}, {'12 pm to': 'QUANTITY'}, {'2 pm': 'TIME'}, {' ': 'ORDINAL'}, {'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}]"
71,"If you’ve ever gone out for a pint in the city, chances are you’ve met Greg Ball. He’s a Kingston bartender who just happens to be signed with....","[{'Greg Ball': 'PERSON'}, {'Kingston': 'GPE'}]"
72,"Swordwall started 8 years ago when some friends working at a restaurant together decided to name the magnetic knife holder in their kitchen, the ""sword wall"".These ...",[{'8 years ago': 'DATE'}]
73,"Lace up your sneakers! Starting April 1st, come join members of the Riverhead team for a bi-weekly 3k walk/run. We will increase distances overtime to keep pace with.....",[{'April 1st': 'DATE'}]
74,Enjoy a family skate on the NHL sized ice pads and then warm up afterwards in the dressing rooms that have in-floor heating. Participants of all ages can enjoy a leisurely skate around the ice surface ...,[{'NHL': 'ORG'}]
75,Come and enjoy Monday night Jazz downtown at Musiikki Cafe.  The number 1 venue for music of all kinds and all places.  Come in and enjoy an expertly made ...,"[{'Monday': 'DATE'}, {'night': 'TIME'}, {'Musiikki Cafe': 'FAC'}, {'1': 'CARDINAL'}]"
76,"The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market is open year-around and sells an assortment of fresh foods, baked goods, crafts and prepared food from....","[{""The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market"": 'ORG'}]"
77,Enjoy indoor ice skating with the whole family at Kingston Memorial Centre each Sunday during the winter season from 12 pm to 2 pm.  Kingston Memorial Centre is situated...,"[{'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}, {'Sunday': 'DATE'}, {'the winter season': 'DATE'}, {'12 pm to': 'QUANTITY'}, {'2 pm': 'TIME'}, {' ': 'ORDINAL'}, {'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}]"
78,"Swordwall started 8 years ago when some friends working at a restaurant together decided to name the magnetic knife holder in their kitchen, the ""sword wall"".These ...",[{'8 years ago': 'DATE'}]
79,"Lace up your sneakers! Starting April 1st, come join members of the Riverhead team for a bi-weekly 3k walk/run. We will increase distances overtime to keep pace with.....",[{'April 1st': 'DATE'}]
80,Enjoy a family skate on the NHL sized ice pads and then warm up afterwards in the dressing rooms that have in-floor heating. Participants of all ages can enjoy a leisurely skate around the ice surface ...,[{'NHL': 'ORG'}]
81,Come and enjoy Monday night Jazz downtown at Musiikki Cafe.  The number 1 venue for music of all kinds and all places.  Come in and enjoy an expertly made ...,"[{'Monday': 'DATE'}, {'night': 'TIME'}, {'Musiikki Cafe': 'FAC'}, {'1': 'CARDINAL'}]"
82,"Enjoy a leisurely skate with friends and family at Centre 70 Arena, 100 Days Road during  the winter season from 4 pm to 5 pm.  The Skate Patrol are on the....","[{'Centre 70 Arena': 'ORG'}, {'100 Days Road': 'CARDINAL'}, {'the winter season': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm to 5 pm': 'TIME'}, {'The Skate Patrol': 'PERSON'}]"
83,"We shuck ’em, you slurp ’em! Tuesday, starting at 4 pm enjoy fresh oysters on the half shell in the Taproom. Shucked to order, paired with Capers homemade.....","[{'Tuesday': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm': 'TIME'}, {'half': 'CARDINAL'}, {'Taproom': 'GPE'}]"
84,"A tradition among jazz lovers, Tuesday Night Jazz at Olivea ...",[{'Tuesday': 'DATE'}]
85,Expand your skill with acrylic paints. This class is made up of working on a series of panels using a variety of painting styles and applications to develop surface textures.....,[]
86,Get Healthy Kingston – Alternative Health & Wellness Mini Expo has been organized by community minded people who want to bring Health & Wellness Education to ....,"[{'Healthy Kingston': 'PERSON'}, {'Health & Wellness Education': 'ORG'}]"
87,"Lace up your sneakers! Starting April 1st, come join members of the Riverhead team for a bi-weekly 3k walk/run. We will increase distances overtime to keep pace with.....",[{'April 1st': 'DATE'}]
88,Enjoy a family skate on the NHL sized ice pads and then warm up afterwards in the dressing rooms that have in-floor heating. Participants of all ages can enjoy a leisurely skate around the ice surface ...,[{'NHL': 'ORG'}]
89,Come and enjoy Monday night Jazz downtown at Musiikki Cafe.  The number 1 venue for music of all kinds and all places.  Come in and enjoy an expertly made ...,"[{'Monday': 'DATE'}, {'night': 'TIME'}, {'Musiikki Cafe': 'FAC'}, {'1': 'CARDINAL'}]"
90,"Enjoy a leisurely skate with friends and family at Centre 70 Arena, 100 Days Road during  the winter season from 4 pm to 5 pm.  The Skate Patrol are on the....","[{'Centre 70 Arena': 'ORG'}, {'100 Days Road': 'CARDINAL'}, {'the winter season': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm to 5 pm': 'TIME'}, {'The Skate Patrol': 'PERSON'}]"
91,"We shuck ’em, you slurp ’em! Tuesday, starting at 4 pm enjoy fresh oysters on the half shell in the Taproom. Shucked to order, paired with Capers homemade.....","[{'Tuesday': 'DATE'}, {'4 pm': 'TIME'}, {'half': 'CARDINAL'}, {'Taproom': 'GPE'}]"
92,"A tradition among jazz lovers, Tuesday Night Jazz at Olivea ...",[{'Tuesday': 'DATE'}]
93,Expand your skill with acrylic paints. This class is made up of working on a series of panels using a variety of painting styles and applications to develop surface textures.....,[]
94,"An Irish Seisiún is an informal gathering at which people play traditional Irish music. All are welcome to bring their instrument and join in on the fun, every Tuesday at The Toucan!...","[{'An Irish Seisiún': 'GPE'}, {'Irish': 'NORP'}, {'Toucan': 'NORP'}]"
95,Enjoy a lovely ice skate with the whole family at Kingston Memorial Centre where the skate patrol are on the ice to monitor the program and are there to provide assistance when required.,[{'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}]
96,Enjoy a lovely ice skate with the whole family at Kingston Memorial Centre where the skate patrol are on the ice to monitor the program and are there to provide assistance when required.,[{'Kingston Memorial Centre': 'FAC'}]
97,Over 500 songs in the repertoire of The Goodnight Irenes. They perform in an intimate venue where the specialty coffee is fine and the whiskey is smooth ...,[{'500': 'CARDINAL'}]
98,Experiential Tourism is growing in popularity come take part in a cool ( not literally) artisan experience. Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery offers ....,[{'Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery': 'ORG'}]
99,You better come grab your seat early! This local favourite will pack our lounge! You never know who will join Chris Jackson on stage...,[{'Chris Jackson': 'PERSON'}]
