[('Murray McLauchlan', 0, 17, 'PERSON'), ('one', 21, 24, 'CARDINAL'), ('Canada', 28, 34, 'GPE'), ('48-year', 105, 112, 'CARDINAL'), ('19', 137, 139, 'CARDINAL')]
[('the fourth week of FebFest', 4, 30, 'DATE'), ('week', 119, 123, 'DATE'), ('Toast', 126, 131, 'ORG'), ('Canadian', 167, 175, 'NORP')]
[('Bundle', 0, 6, 'GPE'), ('Boucher Park', 43, 55, 'LOC'), ('Clarence Street', 59, 74, 'FAC'), ('Springer Market Square', 103, 125, 'FAC'), ('Boucher Park', 184, 196, 'FAC'), ('the whole month of February', 214, 241, 'DATE'), ('Kingston', 288, 296, 'GPE')]
[('Kingston', 102, 110, 'GPE'), ('8 am to 10 pm', 217, 230, 'TIME'), ('Monday', 231, 237, 'DATE'), ('Sunday', 241, 247, 'DATE')]
[('Greg Ball', 71, 80, 'PERSON'), ('Kingston', 89, 97, 'GPE'), ('Ching Music', 143, 154, 'ORG')]
[('Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery', 108, 139, 'ORG')]
[('Chris Jackson', 110, 123, 'PERSON')]
[('NHL', 27, 30, 'ORG'), ('The Centre 70 Arena', 50, 69, 'FAC'), ('the Skate Patrol', 132, 148, 'WORK_OF_ART')]
[('its third year', 41, 55, 'DATE')]
[('Scotty', 44, 50, 'PERSON'), ('Open Mic', 52, 60, 'PERSON'), ('7pm', 74, 77, 'TIME')]
[('Melos', 12, 17, 'ORG'), ('annual', 19, 25, 'DATE'), ("Enjoy Melos'", 66, 78, 'PERSON'), ('Early Music', 98, 109, 'ORG'), ('George', 119, 125, 'PERSON')]
[('Greg Runions', 0, 12, 'PERSON'), ('Canadian', 30, 38, 'NORP'), ('1996', 153, 157, 'DATE'), ('2017', 162, 166, 'DATE'), ("Duke Ellington's", 198, 214, 'PERSON')]
[('Bundle', 0, 6, 'GPE'), ('Boucher Park', 43, 55, 'LOC'), ('Clarence Street', 59, 74, 'FAC'), ('Springer Market Square', 103, 125, 'FAC'), ('Boucher Park', 184, 196, 'FAC'), ('the whole month of February', 214, 241, 'DATE'), ('Kingston', 288, 296, 'GPE')]
[('Kingston', 102, 110, 'GPE'), ('8 am to 10 pm', 217, 230, 'TIME'), ('Monday', 231, 237, 'DATE'), ('Sunday', 241, 247, 'DATE')]
[('2020', 16, 20, 'DATE'), ('Tim Hortons Brier', 21, 38, 'PERSON'), ('AGI', 53, 56, 'ORG'), ('Feb. 29-March 8', 73, 88, 'DATE'), ('Leon’s Centre', 92, 105, 'FAC'), ('Kingston', 118, 126, 'GPE'), ('The Tim Hortons Brier', 127, 148, 'PERSON'), ('Canadian', 179, 187, 'NORP')]
[('Greg Ball', 71, 80, 'PERSON'), ('Kingston', 89, 97, 'GPE')]
[('April 1st', 32, 41, 'DATE')]
[('NHL', 28, 31, 'ORG')]
[('Monday', 15, 21, 'DATE'), ('night', 22, 27, 'TIME'), ('Musiikki Cafe', 45, 58, 'FAC'), ('1', 72, 73, 'CARDINAL')]
[('Brier Patch Fan Zone', 20, 40, 'GPE'), ('tonight', 74, 81, 'TIME'), ('a Music Video Dance Party', 93, 118, 'ORG')]
[('Bundle', 0, 6, 'GPE'), ('Boucher Park', 43, 55, 'LOC'), ('Clarence Street', 59, 74, 'FAC'), ('Springer Market Square', 103, 125, 'FAC'), ('Boucher Park', 184, 196, 'FAC'), ('the whole month of February', 214, 241, 'DATE'), ('Kingston', 288, 296, 'GPE')]
[('Kingston Memorial Centre', 50, 74, 'FAC')]
[('The Art Noise Gallery', 0, 21, 'ORG'), ('this March', 30, 40, 'DATE'), ('Artist Bob Young', 52, 68, 'PERSON'), ('Bob', 70, 73, 'PERSON'), ('BFA (Visual Art — Studio', 86, 110, 'ORG'), ('York University', 115, 130, 'ORG'), ('Toronto', 132, 139, 'GPE')]
[('Anna, Elsa, Kristoff, Hans, Olaf', 55, 87, 'ORG'), ('Sven', 92, 96, 'DATE')]
[('ONE', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('Legends Show', 17, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Tributes', 178, 186, 'ORG'), ('Music Hits', 190, 200, 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('50s and 60s', 210, 221, 'DATE')]
[('Jordan Edward Benjamin', 0, 22, 'PERSON'), ('Canadian-American', 62, 79, 'NORP'), ('Fueled', 132, 138, 'ORG'), ('Ramen', 142, 147, 'NORP'), ('RCA Records', 152, 163, 'ORG')]
[('Kingston', 65, 73, 'GPE'), ('Sydenham Ward', 80, 93, 'FAC'), ('Kingston', 197, 205, 'GPE')]
[('500', 5, 8, 'CARDINAL')]
[('Greg Ball', 71, 80, 'PERSON'), ('Kingston', 89, 97, 'GPE')]
[('Centre 70 Arena', 51, 66, 'ORG'), ('100 Days Road', 68, 81, 'CARDINAL'), ('the winter season', 90, 107, 'DATE'), ('4 pm to 5 pm', 113, 125, 'TIME'), ('The Skate Patrol', 128, 144, 'PERSON')]
[('The Art Noise Gallery', 0, 21, 'ORG'), ('this March', 30, 40, 'DATE'), ('Artist Bob Young', 52, 68, 'PERSON'), ('Bob', 70, 73, 'PERSON'), ('BFA (Visual Art — Studio', 86, 110, 'ORG'), ('York University', 115, 130, 'ORG'), ('Toronto', 132, 139, 'GPE')]
[('Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery', 108, 139, 'ORG')]
[('Chris Jackson', 110, 123, 'PERSON')]
[]
[('Scotty', 44, 50, 'PERSON'), ('Open Mic', 52, 60, 'PERSON'), ('7pm', 74, 77, 'TIME')]
[]
[('Reichenbach', 105, 116, 'PERSON'), ('Moriarty', 144, 152, 'PERSON'), ('Holmes', 161, 167, 'PERSON')]
[('Beethoven', 74, 83, 'PERSON'), ('eighth', 139, 145, 'ORDINAL'), ('ninth', 176, 181, 'ORDINAL'), ('Joy', 194, 197, 'PERSON'), ('250th Ludwig', 205, 217, 'PERSON')]
[('Greg Ball', 71, 80, 'PERSON'), ('Kingston', 89, 97, 'GPE')]
[('NHL', 47, 50, 'ORG')]
[('annual', 40, 46, 'DATE'), ('Little Cataraqui Creek', 110, 132, 'FAC')]
[("The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market", 0, 35, 'ORG')]
[('Kingston Memorial Centre', 50, 74, 'FAC'), ('Sunday', 80, 86, 'DATE'), ('the winter season', 94, 111, 'DATE'), ('12 pm to', 117, 125, 'QUANTITY'), ('2 pm', 126, 130, 'TIME'), (' ', 132, 133, 'ORDINAL'), ('Kingston Memorial Centre', 133, 157, 'FAC')]
[('8 years ago', 18, 29, 'DATE')]
[('NHL', 28, 31, 'ORG')]
[('Monday', 15, 21, 'DATE'), ('night', 22, 27, 'TIME'), ('Musiikki Cafe', 45, 58, 'FAC'), ('1', 72, 73, 'CARDINAL')]
[('30-person', 7, 16, 'CARDINAL')]
[('winter', 52, 58, 'DATE'), ('Forest Therapy', 59, 73, 'ORG')]
[('New Orleans', 34, 45, 'GPE'), ('Jazz', 52, 56, 'ORG'), ('Cajun', 58, 63, 'ORG'), ('Zydeco', 65, 71, 'ORG'), ('R&B', 76, 79, 'ORG'), ('Spencer Evans', 85, 98, 'PERSON'), ('Thousand Islands', 133, 149, 'FAC'), ('The Island Star', 157, 172, 'FAC')]
[('Greg Ball', 71, 80, 'PERSON'), ('Kingston', 89, 97, 'GPE')]
[('Centre 70 Arena', 51, 66, 'ORG'), ('100 Days Road', 68, 81, 'CARDINAL'), ('the winter season', 90, 107, 'DATE'), ('4 pm to 5 pm', 113, 125, 'TIME'), ('The Skate Patrol', 128, 144, 'PERSON')]
[('Tuesday', 29, 36, 'DATE'), ('4 pm', 50, 54, 'TIME'), ('half', 82, 86, 'CARDINAL'), ('Taproom', 100, 107, 'GPE')]
[('Centre 70 Arena', 51, 66, 'ORG'), ('100 Days Road', 68, 81, 'CARDINAL'), ('the winter season', 90, 107, 'DATE'), ('4 pm to 5 pm', 113, 125, 'TIME'), ('The Skate Patrol', 128, 144, 'PERSON')]
[('Tuesday', 29, 36, 'DATE'), ('4 pm', 50, 54, 'TIME'), ('half', 82, 86, 'CARDINAL'), ('Taproom', 100, 107, 'GPE')]
[('Tuesday', 31, 38, 'DATE')]
[]
[('An Irish Seisiún', 0, 16, 'GPE'), ('Irish', 75, 80, 'NORP'), ('Toucan', 175, 181, 'NORP')]
[('Kingston Memorial Centre', 50, 74, 'FAC')]
[('Greg Ball', 71, 80, 'PERSON'), ('Kingston', 89, 97, 'GPE')]
[('Amanda McCauley', 68, 83, 'PERSON'), ('Prizes', 85, 91, 'PERSON'), ('4-pack', 139, 145, 'CARDINAL')]
[('Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery', 108, 139, 'ORG')]
[('Chris Jackson', 110, 123, 'PERSON')]
[('Scotty', 44, 50, 'PERSON'), ('Open Mic', 52, 60, 'PERSON'), ('7pm', 74, 77, 'TIME')]
[('NHL', 47, 50, 'ORG')]
[('Amanda McCauley', 68, 83, 'PERSON'), ('Prizes', 85, 91, 'PERSON'), ('4-pack', 139, 145, 'CARDINAL')]
[('Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery', 108, 139, 'ORG')]
[('Chris Jackson', 110, 123, 'PERSON')]
[('Scotty', 44, 50, 'PERSON'), ('Open Mic', 52, 60, 'PERSON'), ('7pm', 74, 77, 'TIME')]
[('NHL', 47, 50, 'ORG')]
[("The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market", 0, 35, 'ORG')]
[('Kingston Memorial Centre', 50, 74, 'FAC'), ('Sunday', 80, 86, 'DATE'), ('the winter season', 94, 111, 'DATE'), ('12 pm to', 117, 125, 'QUANTITY'), ('2 pm', 126, 130, 'TIME'), (' ', 132, 133, 'ORDINAL'), ('Kingston Memorial Centre', 133, 157, 'FAC')]
[('Greg Ball', 71, 80, 'PERSON'), ('Kingston', 89, 97, 'GPE')]
[('8 years ago', 18, 29, 'DATE')]
[('April 1st', 32, 41, 'DATE')]
[('NHL', 28, 31, 'ORG')]
[('Monday', 15, 21, 'DATE'), ('night', 22, 27, 'TIME'), ('Musiikki Cafe', 45, 58, 'FAC'), ('1', 72, 73, 'CARDINAL')]
[("The Memorial Centre Farmers' Market", 0, 35, 'ORG')]
[('Kingston Memorial Centre', 50, 74, 'FAC'), ('Sunday', 80, 86, 'DATE'), ('the winter season', 94, 111, 'DATE'), ('12 pm to', 117, 125, 'QUANTITY'), ('2 pm', 126, 130, 'TIME'), (' ', 132, 133, 'ORDINAL'), ('Kingston Memorial Centre', 133, 157, 'FAC')]
[('8 years ago', 18, 29, 'DATE')]
[('April 1st', 32, 41, 'DATE')]
[('NHL', 28, 31, 'ORG')]
[('Monday', 15, 21, 'DATE'), ('night', 22, 27, 'TIME'), ('Musiikki Cafe', 45, 58, 'FAC'), ('1', 72, 73, 'CARDINAL')]
[('Centre 70 Arena', 51, 66, 'ORG'), ('100 Days Road', 68, 81, 'CARDINAL'), ('the winter season', 90, 107, 'DATE'), ('4 pm to 5 pm', 113, 125, 'TIME'), ('The Skate Patrol', 128, 144, 'PERSON')]
[('Tuesday', 29, 36, 'DATE'), ('4 pm', 50, 54, 'TIME'), ('half', 82, 86, 'CARDINAL'), ('Taproom', 100, 107, 'GPE')]
[('Tuesday', 31, 38, 'DATE')]
[]
[('Healthy Kingston', 4, 20, 'PERSON'), ('Health & Wellness Education', 127, 154, 'ORG')]
[('April 1st', 32, 41, 'DATE')]
[('NHL', 28, 31, 'ORG')]
[('Monday', 15, 21, 'DATE'), ('night', 22, 27, 'TIME'), ('Musiikki Cafe', 45, 58, 'FAC'), ('1', 72, 73, 'CARDINAL')]
[('Centre 70 Arena', 51, 66, 'ORG'), ('100 Days Road', 68, 81, 'CARDINAL'), ('the winter season', 90, 107, 'DATE'), ('4 pm to 5 pm', 113, 125, 'TIME'), ('The Skate Patrol', 128, 144, 'PERSON')]
[('Tuesday', 29, 36, 'DATE'), ('4 pm', 50, 54, 'TIME'), ('half', 82, 86, 'CARDINAL'), ('Taproom', 100, 107, 'GPE')]
[('Tuesday', 31, 38, 'DATE')]
[]
[('An Irish Seisiún', 0, 16, 'GPE'), ('Irish', 75, 80, 'NORP'), ('Toucan', 175, 181, 'NORP')]
[('Kingston Memorial Centre', 50, 74, 'FAC')]
[('Kingston Memorial Centre', 50, 74, 'FAC')]
[('500', 5, 8, 'CARDINAL')]
[('Kingston Glass Studio & Gallery', 108, 139, 'ORG')]
[('Chris Jackson', 110, 123, 'PERSON')]
